<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Community on</title><link>https://gambitbsm.org/community/</link><description>Recent content in Community on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gambitbsm.org/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Publications</title><link>https://gambitbsm.org/community/publications/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.org/community/publications/</guid><description>ⓘ Info: A full list of GAMBIT publications and proceedings can be found here. Physics Analyses Collider constraints on electroweakinos in the presence of a light gravitino, Eur. Phys. J. C 83 (2023) 6, 493, arXiv:2303.09082.
Supplementary data, including samples: Global fits of simplified models for dark matter with GAMBIT II. Vector dark matter with an s-channel vector mediator, Eur.Phys.J.C 83 (2023) 8, 692, arXiv:2303.08351.
Supplementary data, including samples: Fast and accurate AMS-02 antiproton likelihoods for global dark matter fits, JCAP 08 (2023) 052, arXiv:2303.</description></item><item><title>Talks</title><link>https://gambitbsm.org/community/talks/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.org/community/talks/</guid><description>Here you can find some slides of a few selected talks about GAMBIT.
ⓘ Info: More can be found on individual members&amp;rsquo; personal websites. SpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleThermal WIMPs and the Scale of New Physics DateDecember 2022 LocationSydney, Australia ReasonConference: DSU 2022 LinkLink SpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleGlobal Fits of Dirac Dark Matter Effective Field Theories DateNovember 2022 LocationDurham, UK ReasonSeminar LinkLink SpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleGlobal Fits of Dirac Dark Matter Effective Field Theories DateJuly 2022 LocationVienna, Austria ReasonConference: IDM 2022 LinkLink SpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleThermal WIMPs and the Scale of New Physics DateJuly 2022 LocationBologna, Italy ReasonConference: ICHEP 2022 LinkLink SpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleGlobal Fits of Dirac Dark Matter Effective Field Theories DateMarch 2022 LocationCarleton University, Ottawa, Canada ReasonSeminar: Particle Seminar LinkLink SpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleThermal WIMPs and the scale of new physics DateDecember 2021 LocationKing's College London, UK ReasonSeminar LinkLink SpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleThermal WIMPs and the Scale of New Physics DateAugust 2021 LocationIllinois (online) ReasonConference: COSMO'21 LinkLink SpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleGlobal study of effective Higgs portal dark matter models using GAMBIT DateDecember 2019 LocationSydney ReasonConference: TeVPA (2019) LinkLink SpeakerJanina RenkTitleCosmoBit: Towards Simultaneous Global Fits of Particle Physics and Cosmology DateSeptember 2019 LocationAachen, Germany ReasonConference: Cosmo19 LinkLink SpeakerAndrew FowlieTitleCombined collider constraints on neutralinos and charginos DateAugust 2019 LocationWeihai, China ReasonWorkshop: Tenth Weihai New Physics Meeting LinkLink SpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleDark matter interpretation with global fits DateAugust 2019 LocationSeattle ReasonWorkshop: Dark Matter @ LHC 2019 LinkLink SpeakerPeter AthronTitleNew Physics Interpretations with GAMBIT DateJuly 2019 LocationGhent, Belgium ReasonConference: EPS-HEP LinkLink SpeakerPat ScottTitleSearches for dark matter with GAMBIT DateJuly 2019 LocationBrisbane, Australia ReasonConference: Astronomical Society of Australia Annual Scientific Meeting LinkLink SpeakerAnkit BeniwalTitleGlobal study of effective Higgs portal dark matter models using GAMBIT DateJuly 2019 LocationGhent, Belgium ReasonConference: EPS-HEP 2019 LinkLink SpeakerTomas GonzaloTitleGlobal fits of neutrino and dark matter models with GAMBIT DateJune 2019 LocationMPIK Heidelberg, Germany ReasonSeminar LinkLink SpeakerTomas GonzaloTitleA global fit of the type-I seesaw mechanism DateJune 2019 LocationImperial College London, UK ReasonSeminar LinkLink SpeakerCsaba BalazsTitleThe status of dark matter DateJune 2019 LocationValencia, Spain ReasonConference: Invisibles 2019 LinkLink SpeakerTomas GonzaloTitleStatus of global SUSY fits DateMay 2019 LocationCorpus Christi, Texas, US ReasonConference: SUSY 2019 LinkLink SpeakerPat ScottTitleStatus of non-supersymmetric dark matter theories with GAMBIT DateMay 2019 LocationPoznan, Poland ReasonConference: PRACEDays 2019, EuroHPC Summit LinkLink SpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleInvestigating supersymmetry with GAMBIT DateMay 2019 LocationPoznan ReasonConference: PRACEdays 2019 LinkLink SpeakerPat ScottTitleStatus of non-supersymmetric models with GAMBIT DateApril 2019 LocationObergurgl, Austria ReasonConference: ALPS (Alpine LHC Summit) LinkLink SpeakerBen FarmerTitleStatus of supersymmetric models with GAMBIT DateApril 2019 LocationObergurgl, Austria ReasonConference: ALPS (Alpine LHC Summit) LinkLink SpeakerTomas GonzaloTitleGlobal fits on BSM models DateMarch 2019 LocationMonash University, Australia ReasonSeminar LinkLink SpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleExploring light SUSY with GAMBIT DateMarch 2019 LocationLa Thuile ReasonConference: Moriond QCD 2019 LinkLink SpeakerSebastian HoofTitleAxion Global Fits with Peccei-Quinn Symmetry Breaking Before Inflation using GAMBIT DateOctober 2018 LocationHamburg, Germany ReasonConference: DESY Theory Workshop LinkLink SpeakerBen FarmerTitleGlobal fits in “Beyond the Standard Model” physics DateOctober 2018 LocationDarmstadt, Germany ReasonConference: ISNET-6 LinkLink SpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleCombined collider constraints on neutralinos and charginos with GAMBIT DateOctober 2018 LocationImperial College London ReasonSeminar: 3-PAC seminar LinkLink SpeakerCsaba BalazsTitleSUSY according to GAMBIT DateJuly 2018 LocationBarcelona ReasonConference: SUSY 2018 LinkLink SpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleMSSM global fits with GAMBIT DateJuly 2018 LocationSeoul ReasonConference: ICHEP 2018 LinkLink SpeakerBen FarmerTitleCalculating p-values in Beyond-the-Standard-Model global fits DateJune 2018 LocationMonash University, Melbourne, Australia ReasonSeminar LinkLink SpeakerAnders KvellestadTitleChasing SUSY through parameter space DateJune 2018 LocationAachen ReasonSeminar LinkLink SpeakerTomas GonzaloTitleSterile Neutrinos in GAMBIT DateMay 2018 LocationStavanger, Norway ReasonWorkshop: N-PACT Meeting 2018 LinkLink SpeakerTomas GonzaloTitlePreviously on GAMBIT.</description></item><item><title>Members</title><link>https://gambitbsm.org/community/members/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.org/community/members/</guid><description>About the Community GAMBIT is developed by a growing community of theorists and experimentalists, including members of the ATLAS, Belle-II, CTA, DARWIN, Fermi-LAT, HESS, IceCube, LHCb, NOvA, SHiP, T2K, and XENON experiments, as well as developers of the public theory codes Capt'n General, DarkSUSY, DDCalc, FlexibleSUSY, HEPLike, gamLike, GM2Calc, IsaJet, nulike, SoftSUSY, SuperIso, and Vevacious. ⓘ Info: The GAMBIT Community has a Code of Conduct . Gallery Here are some of our members with links to more information about them.</description></item><item><title>Code of Conduct</title><link>https://gambitbsm.org/community/code_of_conduct/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.org/community/code_of_conduct/</guid><description>As adopted 29.10.2020. In this document we summarise our shared understanding of what constitutes good collaborative behaviour, and how such behaviour should be actively promoted in the GAMBIT Community. The aim of this code is to foster a healthy collaboration environment for all members of our community. Regardless of personal characteristics, seniority, role or contributions within GAMBIT, all members of our community are expected to read this code, and follow it both in spirit and letter.</description></item><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://gambitbsm.org/community/contact/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:22 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.org/community/contact/</guid><description>If you would like to join the GAMBIT commuity, please send an email to GAMBIT community list.
If you are a meeting organiser and looking for a GAMBIT talk, please send an email to the Science Coordinators on the GAMBIT talks list.</description></item></channel></rss>