<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Installation on</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/</link><description>Recent content in Installation on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Getting Started</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/introduction/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/introduction/</guid><description>Introduction Introduction to GAMBIT Evidence for new physics Beyond the Standard Model (BSM) could appear in any observable in particle, astroparticle or nuclear physics. This means that if a BSM model is to be proven or disproven it is necessary to analyse the data from many different experimental sources simultaneously. Global fits attempt to tackle this problem, combining theoretical observable predictions with targeted searches of experimental data.
GAMBIT, the Global And Modular BSM Inference Tool, is one of a number of global fitting software frameworks.</description></item><item><title>Docker Usage</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/docker_usage/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/docker_usage/</guid><description>Docker Usage A pre-built version of GAMBIT is available as a Docker image which can be downloaded and run locally. This is useful for trying out GAMBIT and following the examples on this site without the need to build GAMBIT from source.
ⓘ Info:
The current Docker image is based on GAMBIT v1.1.3, which is outdated and will not provide the latest features. The Docker engine requires administrator privileges in order to be activated.</description></item><item><title>Installation for Linux</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/installation_for_linux/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/installation_for_linux/</guid><description>Installation for Linux ⓘ Info:
If you intend to build the entirety of GAMBIT without optimisation, at least 10GB of RAM is required. Building with optimisation (for performance-critical applications) may require more than 20GB of RAM. If your system does not meet these requirements then consider only partially building GAMBIT, or using the Docker image. This guide assumes some knowledge of bash and the Linux command line. See the Linux command line tutorial ⧉ for a basic introduction.</description></item><item><title>Installation for Windows</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/installation_for_windows/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/installation_for_windows/</guid><description>Installation for Windows Windows is not directly supported by GAMBIT. However, Linux distributions can be installed on Windows machines using WSL or by dual-booting. GAMBIT can then be built within these Linux environments
Running Linux on a Windows machine Installing Windows Subsystem for Linux (WSL) WSL is a tool supplied by Microsoft that allows Linux distributions to be installed on Windows. Follow the installation instructions ⧉ to install it on your system.</description></item><item><title>Installation for macOS</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/installation_for_macos/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/installation/installation_for_macos/</guid><description>Installation for macOS ⓘ Info: This guide has been reproduced from Aaron Vincent&amp;rsquo;s personal page ⧉ Install Xcode command line tools Install Homebrew ⧉ Install the following packages using brew install XXX: brew install gcc lapack boost gsl wget eigen pkg-config cmake libomp 3.5) On a fresh copy of OSX, linking will be fine; however you may find that, many of these will not be properly linked, since many /usr/local/bin directories are not owned by the owner (?</description></item></channel></rss>