<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Help on</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/help/</link><description>Recent content in Help on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/help/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Common Problems and Questions</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/help/common_problems_and_questions/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/help/common_problems_and_questions/</guid><description>Docker I cannot start or run Docker on Linux On Linux, non-sudo users may encounter permission denied or Cannot connect to the Docker daemon. Is the docker daemon running on this host? errors. By default, only sudo users may run Docker commands on Linux (by adding sudo to the start of the command). To allow other users to run commands, a sudo user must created a new group called docker and add users to it:</description></item><item><title>Compiler Matrix</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/help/compiler_matrix/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/help/compiler_matrix/</guid><description>Below is a list of compilers compatible with GAMBIT and different backends and scanners.
ⓘ Info: The backend and scanner entries refer to the form used in GAMBIT, i.e. after any patching or BOSSing applied by the GAMBIT build system. We have also tested various earlier compilers, but not in as much detail. Please let us know if you have information on presently untested combinations (marked with ?, or missing entirely).</description></item><item><title>Known Issues</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/help/known_issues/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/help/known_issues/</guid><description>ⓘ Info: Please report any new unresolved issues here ⧉. Issue Description Error Python error: is a directory, cannot continue when linked to MPICH and executing via mpiexec/mpirun with &amp;gt;1 process In some rare cases, this error will occur when trying to run with multiple MPI processes after having compiled with MPI support via the MPICH libraries. As best we can tell, it is caused by a bug in either the MPICH libraries or some version of the Python runtime libraries.</description></item><item><title>Configuration Examples</title><link>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/help/configuration_examples/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 22:31:46 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://gambitbsm.github.io/documentation/help/configuration_examples/</guid><description>ⓘ Info: Instructions for configuring and compiling GAMBIT can be found in the original paper describing the code arXiv:1705.07908 ⧉. ⓘ Info: For building the entirety of GAMBIT without optimisation, at least 10 GB of RAM is required. The build can be completed with less RAM than this if enough modules are ditched when running cmake, with e.g. cmake -Ditch=&amp;ldquo;ColliderBit;DarkBit&amp;rdquo; .., etc. See arXiv:1705.07908 ⧉ for further details of how to ditch components.</description></item></channel></rss>